<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>HOME on Krishan Singh</title>
    <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in HOME on Krishan Singh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Krishan Singh</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Future Sales</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/b-future-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/b-future-sales/</guid>
      <description>Predicting future sales
This challenge serves as final project for the &amp;ldquo;How to win a data science competition&amp;rdquo; Coursera course.
In this competition we will work with a challenging time-series dataset consisting of daily sales data, kindly provided by one of the largest Russian software firms - 1C Company.
We will predict total sales for every product and store in the next month. By solving this competition you will be able to apply and enhance your data science skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HackerEarth Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/a-object-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/a-object-detection/</guid>
      <description>HackerEarth Image Classification
An e-commerce platform is getting all geared up for a season clearance sale and plans to leverage social media as the primary channel to reach their audiences. The campaign’s target group are individuals/families that have recently posted a picture of their indoor Christmas decor or are traveling during the holidays.
You work at a leading social media platform and your team has been tasked to build a product recommendation engine for consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Salary Predictions</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/sample-project/</guid>
      <description>Predicting salaries on the scraped data from indeed
Covid-19 has impacted our lives greatly but more so has impacted source of income of many, as if things were already not difficult. As an engineering student currently in my 2nd year, I would be sitting for my internships soon, it would be great to have an idea what skills are trending in tech industry, to boost my chances of getting good internships and eventually a good job, in this project, I predict salaries based on the skills, company names, requirements and rating of the company posted in indeed (best job searching site), for which I scraped the site using BeautifulSoup library.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
