<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>PROJECTS on Krishan Singh</title>
    <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/</link>
    <description>Recent content in PROJECTS on Krishan Singh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© Krishan Singh</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Salary Predictions</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/a-salary-pred/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/a-salary-pred/</guid>
      <description>Predicting salaries on the scraped data from indeed
Covid-19 has impacted our lives greatly but more so has impacted source of income of many, as if things were already not difficult. As an engineering student currently in my 2nd year, I would be sitting for my internships soon, it would be great to have an idea what skills are trending in tech industry, to boost my chances of getting good internships and eventually a good job, in this project, I predict salaries based on the skills, company names, requirements and rating of the company posted in indeed (best job searching site), for which I scraped the site using BeautifulSoup library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HackerEarth Image Classification</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/a-object-detection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 30 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/a-object-detection/</guid>
      <description>An e-commerce platform is getting all geared up for a season clearance sale and plans to leverage social media as the primary channel to reach their audiences. The campaign’s target group are individuals/families that have recently posted a picture of their indoor Christmas decor or are traveling during the holidays.
You work at a leading social media platform and your team has been tasked to build a product recommendation engine for consumers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Future Sales</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/b-future-sales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/b-future-sales/</guid>
      <description>Predicting future sales
This challenge serves as final project for the &amp;ldquo;How to win a data science competition&amp;rdquo; Coursera course.
In this competition we will work with a challenging time-series dataset consisting of daily sales data, kindly provided by one of the largest Russian software firms - 1C Company.
We will predict total sales for every product and store in the next month. By solving this competition you will be able to apply and enhance your data science skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AV JOB-A-THON</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/c-job-a-thon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/c-job-a-thon/</guid>
      <description>Health Insurance Lead Prediction Your Client FinMan is a financial services company that provides various financial services like loan, investment funds, insurance etc. to its customers. FinMan wishes to cross-sell health insurance to the existing customers who may or may not hold insurance policies with the company. The company recommend health insurance to it&amp;rsquo;s customers based on their profile once these customers land on the website. Customers might browse the recommended health insurance policy and consequently fill up a form to apply.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Neural Style Transfer</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/d-neural_style_transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/d-neural_style_transfer/</guid>
      <description>Neural Style Transfer App
In this, we download and use a pretrained neural style transfer model by tensorflow, then we preprocess images using tensorflow preprocessing and finally apply style transfer and visualize the result.
Try out the app here !!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emojify</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/f-emojifier/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/f-emojifier/</guid>
      <description>An Emojifier using LSTM network implemented using keras</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mailing Client</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/g-mailing_client/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/g-mailing_client/</guid>
      <description>Mailing Client using python
For gmail : Make sure you have granted permission for both Sender and Receiver to send email and receive email from Unknown sources(External Sources) in Email Account from here
  Fork the repo
  Add a login_credentials.txt file in to read your email and password from which you will send the mail
  Create a message.txt file consisting your message, you can also attach images.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TCP Chat</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/h-tcp-chat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/h-tcp-chat/</guid>
      <description>Terminal based TCP Chat using python
We implement a fully-functioning TCP chat with one server that hosts the chat and multiple clients that connect to it and communicate with each other.
References : https://www.neuralnine.com/tcp-chat-in-python/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DDOS</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/e-ddos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/e-ddos/</guid>
      <description>A simple DDOS script in Python
This program will allow us to flood a server with so many reqeusts that, after a while, it won’t be able to respond anymore and it will go down.
Note : Python may not be the best programming language for this because python does not support real multi-threading (its simulated multi-threading)
Reference: https://www.neuralnine.com/code-a-ddos-script-in-python/</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cash Flow</title>
      <link>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/i-cashflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blaze-fire.github.io/my_portfolio/portfolio/i-cashflow/</guid>
      <description>Cash_Flow - A Transaction Solver
This project generates transactions between a group of 2 - 9 persons and then simplifies their transactions to minimize the cash flow using greedy approach.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
